Guide to the Wallace Gendron papers 1941-1945
Whitman College and Northwest Archives
- Unidentified Photographs; Gendron's Magazines, Postcards, Identifications, and Ephemera, 1942-1976; 3
  - Postcards: Westminster Abbey: The Unknown Warrior Grave, Westminster Abbey, Westminster Abbey: King Henry VII's Chapel, Westminster Abbey: Wolfe Monument, Bridge Hotel at Potter Heigham, "So We'll Meet Again", Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - American Flag Band, Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - History of the Second World War, Published by Marshall Cavendish, Part 1, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - History of the Second World War, Published by Marshall Cavendish, Part 2, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - History of the Second World War, Published by Marshall Cavendish, Part 3, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - History of the Second World War, Published by Marshall Cavendish, Part 4, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - World War II: The 8th AF Strikes, 1975 January (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Target Germany: A Marshall Cavendish World War II Special No. 4, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Gendron's Identifications: Motor Vehicle Operator's Permit, Tobacco Ration Card, Restricted Area Pass, Bondholder Certificate, Permanent Pass Class A, Mammoth Garden Roller Skating Club Membership Card, Disabled American Veterans, 1943-1949 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Miniature Postcards Re: Walla Walla, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Army Air Base Records, Walla Walla, WA, 1941-1944; 4
  - Army Air Base File #000-800, 1941-1942 (Box 5)
  - Army Air Base File #600 Misc., 1943-1944 (Box 3)
- Oversize Maps and Photographs, 1941-1944; 5 (Folder MC.2.5)